[{
       "question":" All keywords in C are in _________?" ,
       "choice1":"LowerCase letters" ,
       "choice2":"UpperCase letters" ,
       "choice3": "CamelCase letters",
       "choice4":" None of the mentioned" ,
       "answer":1

},
   {   
      "question":"Which is valid C expression?",
      "choice1":"int my_num = 100,000;",
      "choice2":"int my_num = 100000;",
      "choice3":"int my num = 1000;",
      "choice4": "int $my_num = 10000;",
      "answer":2
},
{
     "question":"Functions in C Language are always _______",
      "choice1":"Internal",
      "choice2":"External",
      "choice3":"Both Internal and External",
      "choice4": "External and Internal are not valid terms for functions",
      "answer":2
},
{
     "question":"What is meant by ‘a’ in the following C operation?, \n fp = fopen('Random.txt', 'a');",
      "choice1":"Attach",
      "choice2":" Apprehend",
      "choice3":"Append",
      "choice4": "Add",
      "answer":3
},
{
    "question":"What will be the final value of x in the following C code?\n #include <stdio.h>\n void main() \n {\n int x = 5 * 9 / 3 + 9; \n }",
      "choice1":"3.75",
      "choice2":"Depends on compiler",
      "choice3":"24",
      "choice4": "3",
      "answer":3
},
{
    "question":"What will be the data type returned for the following C function \n #include <stdio.h>\n int func()\n{\n return (double)(char)5.0;\n }",
      "choice1":"int",
      "choice2":"char",
      "choice3":"double",
      "choice4": "multiple type-casting in return is illegal",
      "answer":1
},
{
    "question":"What will be the output of the following C code snippet? \n #include <stdio.h> \n void main() \n { \n 1 < 2 ? return 1: return 2;\n }" ,
       "choice1":"returns 1" ,
       "choice2":"returns 2" ,
       "choice3": "Varies",
       "choice4":"Compile time error" ,
       "answer":4
},
   {
     "question":"'Comment on the following C statement \n n = 1; \n printf('%d, %dn', 3*n, n++);'" ,
       "choice1":"Output will be 3, 2" ,
       "choice2":"Output will be 3, 1" ,
       "choice3": "Output will be 6, 1",
       "choice4":"Output is compiler dependent" ,
       "answer":4
},
 {
     "question":" What will be the value of the following assignment expression?\n (x = foo())!= 1 considering foo() returns 2" ,
       "choice1":"2" ,
       "choice2":"True" ,
       "choice3": "1",
       "choice4":"0" ,
       "answer":1
},
{
    "question":"When a C program is started, O.S environment is responsible for opening file and providing pointer for that file?" ,
       "choice1":"Standard input" ,
       "choice2":"Standard output" ,
       "choice3": "Standard error",
       "choice4":"All of the mentioned" ,
       "answer":4
}]